### Contact

Tunis-montfleury +21653573786 (Mobile) abdoumed46574423@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/djeibaba-abdellahi-142968235 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Deep learning
Web Applications
API Development

## Languages

Français (Full Professional)
Anglais (Full Professional)
Arabe (Native or Bilingual)
Espagnol (Professional Working)

### Certifications

Internet of Things (IoT): Fundamental Course (101 level)

Web Development Beginner Bootcamp

Big Data Programming Languages & Big Data Vs Data Science

Data Analytics, Storage, Mining & Visual Big Data Technologies

AutoML Automated Machine Learning BootCamp (No Code ML)

# Djeibaba Abdellahi

Al Software Engineer chez Groupe SFM Grand Tunis Metropolitan Area

# Summary

I specialize in the field of electrical systems and advanced technology, Data Entry, with an advanced specialization in emerging technologies focusing on smart grid, Al analysis, and IoT. I have worked on projects involving Al and renewable energy combined with IoT.

One of the projects I have worked on is the 'Design and Implementation of an Autonomous Smart Home with Camera Surveillance (Face Detection) Powered by Solar Energy (Solar Tracker)'. This project integrates renewable energy technologies, AI, and IoT.

You will find detailed descriptions of real projects I have undertaken throughout my career in my profile.

# Experience

Groupe SFM
Al Software Engineer
February 2024 - Present (6 months)
Gouvernorat Tunis, Tunisie

Groupe SFM Electrical Engineer February 2023 - August 2023 (7 months) Tunis, Tunisia

\*Master's Thesis Internship\*

Design and Implementation of an Autonomous Smart Home with Camera Surveillance Powered by Solar Energy (Solar Tracker)

SOMELEC Software Application Engineer April 2021 - July 2021 (4 months) Nouakchott, Mauritania \*Bachelor's Thesis Internship\*

Development of an API interface for managing a solar park connected to the grid

#### **IBS**

Wep developper

September 2019 - December 2019 (4 months)

Mauritania

\*volunteer internship\*

Development of mobile applications for publishing the company's products

## Education

Université de Tunis

Engineering, Advanced Technology · (September 2022 - July 2024)

Université de Tunis

Master's degree, Electrical Systems and Advanced Technology · (September 2023 - October 2024)

Université Tunis Carthage

Master's degree, Electronics, Electrical, and Automation · (September 2021 - May 2023)

Université de Nouakchott Al Aasriya (University of Nouakchott Al Aasriya)

Bachelor's Degree , Renewable Energy Systems · (September 2019 - July 2021)

Université Tunis Carthage

Master's degree, Électronique electrotechnique et automatique · (September 2021 - September 2023)